Juan Noyola QA Engineer

+52 419 107 7741



noyolaund@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/noyola-juan/



Querétaro, México

EXPERIENCE

2022 - Present

QA / SDET

Deloitte - Texas Instruments

Develop and improve **Test Suites**, failure analysis and **debug**. Functional, Regression, Exploratory and Power Management testing. **JIRA / Confluence** / Bitbucket / **GIT / BLEA / Firmware validation / Manual and Automated Testing / Robot Framework / Jenkins / Python / Unit Test**

2021 - 2022

QA Automation Engineer

Wipro Limited - Ford

Design and build manual/automated **test cases** based on test scenarios for automotive clusters using a framework written on **Python** (Object Oriented Programming), CAN Bus and serial communications, data log **analysis**, defect analysis, RTC Manager. Vector Tools Basics, Tracer, Eclipse, **Jenkins**.

2020 - 2021

Embedded Test Engineer

Dextra Technologies - Verizon

Planning and build manual/automated test cases for a tracking device designed by Verizon IoT division. Reading and analyze log files using communications like CAN Bus, RS232 and serial ports. Device Feature testing (GPS, Wi-Fi, Bluetooth, Accelerometer). QA Software / Black - White Box Testing.

2019 - 2020

Test Content Engineer

UST Global - Intel Corp.

Perform manual/automated test cases according to the SW test specification. Develop scripts to automate software tests for non-volatile memory in python language, Windows and Linux server management and config. Jira ticket system. Firmware Test, bash, batch and C scripting, yaml & json config files, debug analysis. Agile & Scrum methodologies. Migrate the entire automation framework from Python 2 to Python 3.

EDUCATION

2023

ISTQB Foundation Level

Udemv

ISTQB Certified Tester Foundation Level (CTFL) v4.0 (2023)

2013-2018

Electronics Engineer

Tecnológico Nacional de México - Campus Querétaro

Electronics Engineer – Digital and Wireless Communications

STATEMENT

QA Engineer with over 5+ years in testing experience, **Python** Automation - Software Developer - Black Box and White Box Testing - Hardware Testing & Embedded Devices. Failure and Debug Analysis.

Structured and Object-Oriented Programming. Strengths in Python, C and C++. Git & Bitbucket, RTOS Basics and Linux environment, Bash scripting. InfoSec practices, Server Management, Jira / Confluence.

Full Time Gamer!

SKILLS

Professional

| Debug analysis | Python | |
|----------------|----------------|--|
| | Debug analysis | |
| Test Design | Test Design | |
| API Testing | API Testing | |
| Selenium | Selenium | |
| GitHub | GitHub | |
| JIRA | JIRA | |

Personal

| Personal | |
|---------------|--|
| Creativity | |
| Communication | |
| Hard Work | |
| Gamer | |